Guide to the R.C. Maxwell Company Records, 1891-2001 and undated RL.01071
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographs NOT Included in the ROAD Database, 1951-1991 and undated, 100 boxes
  - 1956 Mar.-1957 May 31, 94 folders (Box NP34)
    - Maxwell 15709-15857 (Box NP34)
  - 1957 June 5-1957 July 6, 81 folders (Box NP35)
    - Maxwell 15863-15985 (Box NP35)
  - 1957 July 6-1957 Aug. 27, 87 folders (Box NP36)
    - Maxwell 15986-16128 (Box NP36)
  - 1957 Aug. 27-1957 Sept. 13, 94 folders (Box NP37)
    - Maxwell 16129-16309 (Box NP37)
  - 1957 Sept. 18-1957 Nov. 7, 86 folders (Box NP38)
    - Maxwell 16313-16430 (Box NP38)
  - 1957 Nov. 20-1958 Jan. 30, 96 folders (Box NP39)
    - Maxwell 16432-16568 (Box NP39)
  - 1958 Feb. 3-1958 Apr. 21, 90 folders (Box NP40)
    - Maxwell 16569-16736 (Box NP40)
  - 1958 Apr. 23-1958 July 3, 103 folders (Box NP41)
    - Maxwell 16737-16927 (Box NP41)
  - 1958 June 4-1958 Aug. 5, 97 folders (Box NP42)
    - Maxwell 16928-17063 (Box NP42)
  - 1958 Aug. 5-1958 Sept. 1, 104 folders (Box NP43)
    - Maxwell 17064-17207 (Box NP43)
  - 1958 Sept. 1-1958 Sept. 22, 78 folders (Box NP44)
    - Maxwell 17205-17332 (Box NP44)
  - 1958 Sept. 22-1959 Jan. 2, 104 folders (Box NP45)
    - Maxwell 17333-17470 (Box NP45)
  - 1959 Jan. 2-1959 Mar. 24, 108 folders (Box NP46)
    - Maxwell 17471-17633 (Box NP46)
  - 1959 Mar. 28-1959 May 26, 114 folders (Box NP47)
    - Maxwell 17634-17848 (Box NP47)
  - 1959 May 27-1959 July 29, 102 folders (Box NP48)
    - Maxwell 17853-18158 (Box NP48)
  - 1959 July 28-1959 Oct. 26, 126 folders (Box NP49)
    - Maxwell 18168-18527 (Box NP49)
  - 1959 Oct.-1960 Apr. 14, 118 folders (Box NP50)
    - Maxwell 18552-18827 (Box NP50)
  - 1960 Apr. 16-1960 July 21, 132 folders (Box NP51)
    - Maxwell 18828-19142 (Box NP51)
  - 1960 July 21-1960 Oct., 107 folders (Box NP52)
    - Maxwell 19167-19617 (Box NP52)
  - 1960 Oct.-1961 Mar. 21, 116 folders (Box NP53)
    - Maxwell 19620-19864 (Box NP53)
  - 1961 Mar. 27-1961 July 2, 111 folders (Box NP54)
    - Maxwell 19865-20138 (Box NP54)
  - 1961 July 2-1961 Oct. 10, 112 folders (Box NP55)
    - Maxwell 20141-20620 (Box NP55)
  - 1961 Oct. 11-1962 Mar. 23, 109 folders (Box NP56)
    - Maxwell 20626-20883 (Box NP56)
  - 1962 Mar. 23-1962 July 12, 96 folders (Box NP57)
    - Maxwell 20886-21231 (Box NP57)
  - 1962 July 19-1962 Nov. 13, 102 folders (Box NP58)
    - Maxwell 21232-21661 (Box NP58)
  - 1962 Nov. 13-1963 May 6, 109 folders (Box NP59)
    - Maxwell 21662-21908 (Box NP59)
  - 1963 May 6-1963 June 25, 106 folders (Box NP60)
    - Maxwell 21909-22106 (Box NP60)
  - 1963 June 25-1963 Dec. 16, 81 folders (Box NP61)
    - Maxwell 22107-22620 (Box NP61)
  - [Box number not used in final processing.] (Box NP62)
  - 1963 Dec.-1964 Aug. 20, 89 folders (Box NP63)
    - Maxwell 22628-23193 (Box NP63)
  - 1964 Aug. 21-1965 Aug. 4, 112 folders (Box NP64)
    - Maxwell 23217-23899 (Box NP64)
  - 1965 Aug. 5-1967 Mar. 26, 156 folders (Box NP65)
    - Maxwell 23907-25144 (Box NP65)
  - 1967 Mar. 26-1968 May 9, 99 folders (Box NP66A)
    - Maxwell 25156-25845 (Box NP66A)
  - 1968 May 3-1969 Jan. 15, 50 folders (Box NP66B)
    - Maxwell 25846-26248 (Box NP66B)
  - 1969 Jan. 20-1971 Feb. 9, 139 folders (Box NP67)
    - Maxwell 26249-27201 (Box NP67)
  - 1971 Feb. 11-1972 Aug. 9, 145 folders (Box NP68)
    - Maxwell 27202-27931 (Box NP68)
  - 1972 Aug. 9-1974 Jan. 15, 129 folders (Box NP69)
    - Maxwell 27934-28747 (Box NP69)
  - 1974 Jan. 16-1975 Dec. 15, 133 folders (Box NP70)
    - Maxwell 28748-29503 (Box NP70)
  - 1976 Jan. 2-1978 Sept. 20, 128 folders (Box NP71)
    - Maxwell 29504-30116 (Box NP71)
  - 1978 Sept. 21-1981 Aug. 1, 129 folders (Box NP72)
    - Maxwell 30117-30968 (Box NP72)
  - 1981 Aug. 1-1982 Nov. 9, 130 folders (Box NP73)
    - Maxwell 30969-31619 (Box NP73)
  - 1982 Nov. 9-1983 Sept. 6, 175 folders (Box NP74)
    - Maxwell 31620-32121 (Box NP74)
  - 1983 Sept. 6-1984 May 17, 165 folders (Box NP75)
    - Maxwell 32122-32596 (Box NP75)
  - 1984 May 22-1985 Feb. 4, 130 folders (Box NP76)
    - Maxwell 32601-33085 (Box NP76)
  - 1985 Feb. 14-1985 Aug. 28, 114 folders (Box NP77)
    - Maxwell 33086-33439 (Box NP77)
  - 1985 Aug. 28-1986 Aug. 19, 113 folders (Box NP78)
    - Maxwell 33440-34022 (Box NP78)
  - 1986 Aug. 25-1987 Apr. 21, 122 folders (Box NP79)
    - Maxwell 34024-345070 (Box NP79)
  - 1987 Apr. 21-1988 Aug. 2, 102 folders (Box NP80)
    - Maxwell 34508-35627 (Box NP80)
  - 1988 Aug. 2-1990 Mar. 12, 56 folders (Box NP81)
    - Maxwell 35628-37423 (Box NP81)
  - 1990 Mar. 12-1990 Oct. 19, 112 folders (Box NP82)
    - Maxwell 37424-38287 (Box NP82)
  - 1990 Oct. 30-1991 May 21, 104 folders (Box NP83)
    - Maxwell 38288-38840 (Box NP83)
  - Loose Photographs
    - Maxwell X12-X17-32, [-16]-17-18 Series, 3-16--73-18, 8-290--8-1684, 1-154 (Box NP84)
    - Maxwell 184-2826 (Box NP85)
    - Maxwell 2827-5789 (Box NP86)
    - Maxwell 6103-10999 (Box NP87)
    - Maxwell 11096-11448 (Box NP88)
    - Maxwell 11449-11960 (Box NP89)
    - Maxwell 11962-14731 (Box NP90)
    - Maxwell 14868-17220 (Box NP91)
    - Maxwell 17224-19743 (Box NP92)
    - Maxwell 19782-22595 (Box NP93)
  - Unnumbered Photographs
    - 1910s-1931 (Box NP94)
    - 1931-1934 (Box NP95)
    - 1934-1935 (Box NP96)
    - 1935-1937 (Box NP97)
    - 1937-1939 (Box NP98)
    - 1930s Misc.-1941 (Box NP99)
    - 1941-1964 and undated (Box NP100)
- Negatives, 1916-1991 and undated (Restricted), 112 boxes
  Negatives from both the Photographs Included in the ROAD Database Series, and the Photographs NOT Included in the ROAD Database Series are found here. The series is divided into Glass Plate Negatives and Film Negatives, and follow a chronological order where possible. In general, boxes NN1-NN43 contain negatives from those photographs included in ROAD, and boxes NN43-NN87 contain negatives from those photographs NOT included in the ROAD database. However, a few negatives in boxes NN-NN43 are missing corresponding photographs for documentation in the ROAD database.
  Restriction on Access: Negatives are restricted for preservation reasons. Patrons should view prints. Requests to view negatives under special circumstances may be submitted to the Head of Research Services and will be considered on a case-by-case basis.
  - Glass plate negatives, 1916-1918 and undated
    - Plate with conservation problem, undated, 1 plate (Box NN1)
    - Unnumbered (product and non-product), undated, 27 plates (Box NN2)
    - A Series and 8- Series, undated, 40 plates (Box NN3)
    - 1916, 42 plates (Box NN4)
      - Maxwell [4-16/5-16]-[117-16] (Box NN4)
    - 1916-1917, 40 plates (Box NN5)
      - Maxwell [118-16]-[145-16], [2-17]-[57-17] (Box NN5)
    - 1917, 42 plates (Box NN6)
      - Maxwell [59-17]-[193-17] (Box NN6)
    - [circa 1918], 40 plates (Box NN7)
      - Maxwell 7-181 (Box NN7)
    - [circa 1918], 42 plates (Box NN8)
      - Maxwell 182-227 (Box NN8)
    - [circa 1918], 43 plates (Box NN9)
      - Maxwell 229-279 (Box NN9)
    - [circa 1918], 33 plates (Box NN10)
      - Maxwell 281-305, 921-936 (Box NN10)
    - Unnumbered Non-Product, undated, 1 plate (Box NN11)
    - 8X10 Plate, undated, 1 plate (Box NN12)
    - 5x7 plates, Maxwell A7-A55, [7-16]-[13-16] (Box NN12A)
    - 5x7 plates, Maxwell [11-17]-68-17] (Box NN12B)
    - 5x7 plates, Maxwell [69-17]-80-18], 2-37 (Box NN12C)
    - 5x7 plates, Maxwell 38-[167-2] (Box NN12D)
    - 5x7 plates, Maxwell 186-280 (Box NN12E)
    - 5x7 plates, unnumbered, undated (Box NN12F)
    - 8x10 plates, Maxwell 144-[685-2] (Box NN12G)
  - Film Negatives, 1932-1963 and undated
    - 1932-1933, 52 folders (Box NN13)
      - No Maxwell numbers (Box NN13)
    - 1933-1949, 52 folders (Box NN14)
      - No Maxwell numbers (Box NN14)
    - Undated, 7 folders (Box NN15)
      - Unnumbered, Non-Product, and Maxwell [13]8-611-[173], [8]811-1840 (Box NN15)
    - Undated, 8 folders (Box NN16)
      - Maxwell 1001-5421 (Box NN16)
    - [Box number not used in final processing] (Box NN17)
    - 1935 Oct.-1937 Jan., 7 folders (Box NN18)
      - Maxwell 3743-4344 (Box NN18)
    - 1937 Feb.-1937 Sept., 6 folders (Box NN19)
      - Maxwell 4345-4744 (Box NN19)
    - 1937 Sept.-1938 July, 6 folders (Box NN20)
      - Maxwell 4745-5199 (Box NN20)
    - 1938 July-1939 Apr., 7 folders (Box NN21)
      - Maxwell 5200-5494 (Box NN21)
    - 1939 Apr.-1939 July, 8 folders (Box NN22)
      - Maxwell 5495-5654 (Box NN22)
    - 1939 July-1939 Sept., 7 folders (Box NN23)
      - Maxwell 5655-5794 (Box NN23)
    - 1939 Sept.-1939 Dec., 5 folders (Box NN24)
      - Maxwell 5795-5907 (Box NN24)
    - 1939 Dec.-1940 Sept., 115 folders (Box NN25)
      - Maxwell 5908-6138 (Box NN25)
    - 1940 Dec.-1941 May, 97 folders (Box NN26)
      - Maxwell 6139-6348 (Box NN26)
    - 1941 May-1941 Nov., 115 folders (Box NN27)
      - Maxwell 6349-6538 (Box NN27)
    - 1941 Nov.-1942 Apr., 135 folders (Box NN28)
      - Maxwell 6539-6648 (Box NN28)
    - 1942 Apr.-1945 Aug., 109 folders (Box NN29)
      - Maxwell 6649-6813 (Box NN29)
    - 1945 Sept.-1946 Apr., 84 folders (Box NN30)
      - Maxwell 6816-7052 (Box NN30)
    - 1946 Apr.-1946 Sept., 92 folders (Box NN31)
      - Maxwell 7053-7238 (Box NN31)
    - 1946 Sept., 68 folders (Box NN32)
      - Maxwell 7239-7439 (Box NN32)
    - 1946 Sept.-1946 Dec., 87 folders (Box NN33)
      - Maxwell 7440-7655 (Box NN33)
    - 1946 Dec.-1947 June, 70 folders (Box NN34)
      - Maxwell 7656-7992 (Box NN34)
    - 1947 July-1947 Oct., 87 folders (Box NN35)
      - Maxwell 7993-8200 (Box NN35)
    - 1947 Oct. 1948 May, 83 folders (Box NN36)
      - Maxwell 8201-8507 (Box NN36)
    - 1948 June-1950 Mar., 129 folders (Box NN37)
      - Maxwell 8529-9865 (Box NN37)
    - 1950 Mar.-1950 Nov., 127 folders (Box NN38)
      - Maxwell 9866-10281 (Box NN38)
    - 1950 Nov.-1951 Mar., 131 folders (Box NN39)
      - Maxwell 10282-10499 (Box NN39)
    - 1951 Mar.-1951 July, 140 folders (Box NN40)
      - Maxwell 10501-10835 (Box NN40)
    - 1951 July-1951 Oct., 98 folders (Box NN41)
      - Maxwell 10836-11093 (Box NN41)
    - 1952 Mar.-1952 Nov., 106 folders (Box NN42)
      - Maxwell 11322-119001952 (Box NN42)
    - 1952 Nov,-1953 Apr., 105 folders (Box NN43)
      - Maxwell 11901-12124 (Box NN43)
    - 1953 Apr.-1953 June, 135 folders (Box NN44)
      - Maxwell 12125-12255 (Box NN44)
    - 1953 Sept., 14 folders (Box NN45)
      - Maxwell 12462-12604 (Box NN45)
    - 1953 Oct.-1953 Nov., 19 folders (Box NN46)
      - Maxwell 12605-12808 (Box NN46)
    - 1953 Dec.-1954 Apr., 10 folders (Box NN47)
      - Maxwell 12809-12976 (Box NN47)
    - 1954 Apr.-1954 May, 11 folders (Box NN48)
      - Maxwell 12990-13103 (Box NN48)
    - 1954 May-1954 July, 9 folders (Box NN49)
      - Maxwell 13104-13236 (Box NN49)
    - 1954 July-1954 Aug., 12 folders (Box NN50)
      - Maxwell 13237-13425 (Box NN50)
    - 1954 Aug.-1954 Sept., 10 folders (Box NN51)
      - Maxwell 13426-13617 (Box NN51)
    - 1954 Sept.-1955 Feb., 8 folders (Box NN52)
      - Maxwell 13618-13845 (Box NN52)
    - 1955 Feb.-1955 Apr., 10 folders (Box NN53)
      - Maxwell 13845b-14020 (Box NN53)
    - 1955 Apr.-1955 June, 9 folders (Box NN54)
      - Maxwell 14021-14216 (Box NN54)
    - 1955 July-1955 Aug., 10 folders (Box NN55)
      - Maxwell 14217-14422 (Box NN55)
    - 1955 Sept.-1955 Nov., 11 folders (Box NN56)
      - Maxwell 14423-14604 (Box NN56)
    - 1955 Dec.-1956 Apr., 12 folders (Box NN57)
      - Maxwell 14605-14830 (Box NN57)
    - 1956 Apr.-1956 June, 10 folders (Box NN58)
      - Maxwell 14831-15024 (Box NN58)
    - 1956 June-1956 July, 7 folders (Box NN59)
      - Maxwell 15025-15191 (Box NN59)
    - 1956 July-1956 Sept., 10 folders (Box NN60)
      - Maxwell 15192-15408 (Box NN60)
    - 1956 Sept.-1957 Jan., 10 folders (Box NN61)
      - Maxwell 15409-15623 (Box NN61)
    - 1957 Feb.-1957 June, 11 folders (Box NN62)
      - Maxwell 15624-15880 (Box NN62)
    - 1957 June-1957 Aug., 10 folders (Box NN63)
      - Maxwell 15881-16099 (Box NN63)
    - 1957 Aug.-1957 Oct., 10 folders (Box NN64)
      - Maxwell 16122-16422 (Box NN64)
    - 1957 Nov.-1958 Apr., 10 folders (Box NN65)
      - Maxwell 16423-16693 (Box NN65)
    - 1958 Apr.-1958 July, 11 folders (Box NN66)
      - Maxwell 16694-16972 (Box NN66)
    - 1958 July-1958 Sept., 9 folders (Box NN67)
      - Maxwell 16973-17300 (Box NN67)
    - 1958 Sept.-1959 Mar., 10 folders (Box NN68)
      - Maxwell 17301-17581 (Box NN68)
    - 1959 Mar.-1959 May, 8 folders (Box NN69)
      - Maxwell 17582-17823 (Box NN69)
    - 1959 May-1959 July, 10 folders (Box NN70)
      - Maxwell 17834-18127 (Box NN70)
    - 1959 July-1959 Sept., 9 folders (Box NN71)
      - Maxwell 18129-18428 (Box NN71)
    - 1959 Sept.-1960 Feb., 15 folders (Box NN72)
      - Maxwell 18429-18735 (Box NN72)
    - 1960 Feb.-1960 June, 9 folders (Box NN73)
      - Maxwell 18736-19021 (Box NN73)
    - 1960 June-1960 Aug., 12 folders (Box NN74)
      - Maxwell 19022-19274 (Box NN74)
    - 1960 Aug.-1960 Nov., 8 folders (Box NN75)
      - Maxwell 19275-19573 (Box NN75)
    - 1960 Nov.-1961 Mar., 11 folders (Box NN76)
      - Maxwell 19574-19850 (Box NN76)
    - 1961 Mar.-1961 July, 8 folders (Box NN77)
      - Maxwell 19851-20186 (Box NN77)
    - 1961 July-1961 Sept., 12 folders (Box NN78)
      - Maxwell 20187-20567 (Box NN78)
    - 1961 Sept.-1962 Mar., 13 folders (Box NN79)
      - Maxwell 20568-20859 (Box NN79)
    - 1962 Mar.-1962 July, 13 folders (Box NN80)
      - Maxwell 20860-21212 (Box NN80)
    - 1962 July-1962 Aug., 6 folders, box is not full (Box NN81)
      - Maxwell 21213-21394 (Box NN81)
    - 1962 Aug.-1962 Nov., 10 folders (Box NN82)
      - Maxwell 21395-21648 (Box NN82)
    - 1962 Nov.-1963 Apr., 10 folders (Box NN83)
      - Maxwell 21649-21856 (Box NN83)
    - 1963 Apr.-1963 June, 11 folders (Box NN84)
      - Maxwell 21857-22081 (Box NN84)
    - 1963 June-1963 Aug., 10 folders (Box NN85)
      - Maxwell 22082-22311 (Box NN85)
    - 1963 Aug.-1963 Nov., 8 folders (Box NN86)
      - Maxwell 22312-22582 (Box NN86)
    - 1963 Nov.-1963 Dec., 2 folders, box is not full (Box NN87)
      - Maxwell 22583-22623 (Box NN87)
    - 1963-1965, 10 folders (Box NN88)
      - Maxwell 22628-23599 (Box NN88)
    - 1965-1967, 8 folders (Box NN89)
      - Maxwell 23600-25077 (Box NN89)
    - 1967-1970, 8 folders (Box NN90)
      - Maxwell 25078-26646 (Box NN90)
    - 1970-1975, 7 folders (Box NN91)
      - Maxwell 26647-29157 (Box NN91)
    - 1975-1980, 8 folders (Box NN92)
      - Maxwell 29158-30505 (Box NN92)
    - 1980-1983, 12 folders (Box NN93)
      - Maxwell 30506-32099 (Box NN93)
    - 1980-1985, 91 folders (Box NN94)
      - Maxwell 32102-33415 (Box NN94)
    - 1985-1986, 116 folders (Box NN95)
      - Maxwell 33416-34029 (Box NN95)
    - 1986-1987, 100 folders (Box NN96)
      - Maxwell 34030-35026 (Box NN96)
    - 1987-1991, 34 folders (Box NN97)
      - Maxwell 35033-38840 (Box NN97)
    - Loose Negatives
      - Maxwell 2169-11110 (Box NN98)
      - Maxwell 11111-11458 (Box NN99)
      - Maxwell 11460-11676 (Box NN100)
      - Maxwell 11842-21720 (Box NN101)
    - Unnumbered Negatives
      - 1910s-1938 (Box NN102)
      - 1938-1940 (Box NN103)
      - 1940-1950s and undated (Box NN104)
      - Damaged negatives (Box NN105)
      - Office Files--negatives from Public Relations files (Box NN106)
    - Nitrate Negatives
      Restrictions on Access: Nitrate negatives are closed to researchers.
      - Maxwell x12, x24, [8-618]-[8-1212], 1-5185, unnumbered circa 1924-1931 (Box NIT1)
      - Unnumbered, 1931-1932 (Box NIT2)
      - Unnumbered, 1932-1934 (Box NIT3)
      - Unnumbered, 1935-1937 (Box NIT4)
      - Unnumbered, 1937-1939, circa 1930s (Box NIT5)
      - Unnumbered, circa 1930s-1940s and undated (Box NIT6)